SAORIOKAWA

Certified UX Designer / MSc Management

CONTACT

- +31642947663
- ✓ saoriokawa@gmail.com
- The Hague
- saoriokawa.webflow.io
- in www.linkedin.com/in/saoriokawa
- Bē www.behance.net/saoriokawa

TOOLS

Sketch FlowMapp
InVision Usability Hub
Adobe XD Optimal Workshop
Balsamiq MS Office

UX SKILLS

Competitive Analysis

User Interviews

User Personas

Journey Maps

Information Architecture

Wireframing and Prototyping

Usability Testing

LANGUAGES

JAPANESE: Native ENGLISH: Fluent DUTCH: Basic ITALIAN: Basic



PROFILE

I am a teacher-turned-UX designer with curiosity in understanding people as well as organisational skills to make complicated information easy to comprehend.

I can offer a high sensitivity for details and rigidity in getting a job done, which I have acquired through my four years of experience as a translation checker.



EDUCATION

2018-

UX Design Course

Current CareerFoundry

• Developed several real-world projects during the course, using software such as Adobe XD, Sketch and Balsamiq.

2011-13

MSc Management with Merit

University of Leicester, UK

2007-11

BA Intercultural Studies with GPA 3.6

Kobe University, Japan



WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2016-Current

Freelancer

rent The Netherlands

- Moving to a foreign country and working as as self-employed.
- Providing translation check service between Japanese and English.
- Managing translation projects.
- Giving Japanese/English lessons.

APR 2015-AUG 2016

Quality Control Manager

ASCA Corporation, Japan

- Managing medical translation projects contacting clients and contractors.
- Coordinating courses in medical patent translation.
- Spreading the use of a translation software among company and its contractors.

JAN 2014-MAR 2015

English Instructor

ECC, Japan

- Teaching English to students including kids and adults.
- Managing 16 classes with about 100 students in total cooperating with school staff.

APR 2013-NOV 2013

Transactional Specialist

Arvato Digital Services, Singapore

- Corresponding to email enquiries to process registration and to make contracts.
- Checking contracts written in Japanese and English.